{
	"data": [
        {
            "question": "If Robert listened to me more, he ___ understand me better.\n",
            "a": "might",
            "b": "may",
            "c": "must",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "17",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you're a member of the sports centre, you ___ pay to use the tennis courts. They're free to members.\n",
            "a": "can't",
            "b": "mustn't",
            "c": "don't have to",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "17",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was ill last week so I ___ stay in bed for a few days.\n",
            "a": "had to",
            "b": "must",
            "c": "should",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "17",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "___ wear some good boots when you go out. It's very icy.\n",
            "a": "You would",
            "b": "You'd better",
            "c": "You needn't",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "17",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "People ___ throw plastic bags into the sea. They're dangerous for birds and fish.\n",
            "a": "had better not",
            "b": "had better not to",
            "c": "shouldn't",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "17",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "It ___ be lovely to have a fan in the sitting room. It gets very hot in there sometimes. Shall we get one?\n",
            "a": "must",
            "b": "could",
            "c": "would",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "17",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "When we were children we _________ ride our bicycles very fast down a steep hill on the way home from school.\n",
            "a": "must",
            "b": "may",
            "c": "would",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "17",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you're a member of the sports centre, you ___ pay to use the tennis courts. They're free to members.\n",
            "a": "can't",
            "b": "mustn't",
            "c": "don't have to",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "17",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Ben _________ walk to work. He could get the bus, but he walks because he likes the exercise.\n",
            "a": "doesn't have to",
            "b": "mustn't",
            "c": "can't",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "17",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "___ know a lot about animals for this job?\n",
            "a": "Are you able to",
            "b": "Could you",
            "c": "Do you have to",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "17",
            "type": "2"
        }
    ]
}